[
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a small town in Rome",
    "choices": [
      "Dragonby",
      "Margidunum ",
      "Calverton ",
      "Besthorpe"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "From which age is the Museum's metalwork from Attenborough",
    "choices": [
      "Iron Age",
      "Numismatic Collections",
      "Post Medieval",
      "Bronze Age"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "From which country can our Etruscan urn be found?",
    "choices": [
      "Italy",
      "Greece",
      "England",
      "Egypt"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "In which time period do our 'coin flan moulds' originate from?",
    "choices": [
      "2nd c BC",
      "10th c BC",
      "1st c AD",
      "4th c AD"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which medieval site was located on our very own University Park Campus?",
    "choices": [
      "Broughton Lodge",
      "Dragonby",
      "Attenborough",
      "Keighton"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following were found in Nottingham's caves?",
    "choices": [
      "Glass",
      "Pottery",
      "Axes",
      "Coins"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "From which age is the museum's oldest coin",
    "choices": [
      "Palaeolithic",
      "Iron Age",
      "Bronze Age",
      "Neolithic"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of objects were found in Cyprus?",
    "choices": [
      "Pottery ",
      "Glass",
      "Coins",
      "Axe"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "In which city was the cemetery at Ancaster?",
    "choices": [
      "Rome",
      "Athens",
      "Nottingham",
      "Ephesus"
    ],
    "rightAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "From which town was Anglo Saxon pottery be found?",
    "choices": [
      "Dragonby",
      "Kingston on Soar",
      "Besthorpe",
      "Calverton "
    ],
    "rightAnswer": 1
  }
]